Hello Hello friends Welcome my channel
friends today I am going to tell you
how can you cancel such Kapoor Angel's insurance policy any of your followers you can come
here and cancel it easily so Shiv
what do you have to do custom if they want to contact you and
send you a request then how will you do it I am going to
tell you in this video
friends you keep bringing media players like channel Sab Prem Nagar channel Safed
Parli
now friends how to do that
through email so how do you get a crush email ID if you do
n't have a creator email ID then
I will give you the link below it is digital
you go and see it then I will give you the link in the video
I made this there was a doll on it too how
can you register email ID, the
registered email ID is clear then if you do
n't have a registered email ID then you
can click on the link given below and see in the video
what kind of relationship you can make after that
only after you register here you will
not be able to come here and cancel it now by going to Krishi then
you will get a quick
response in minutes if you don't do it then you will get a call from here and then the
process will
not be done quickly  So if you don't have them then
restore email
below and I have given parinde, you can do it by
watching the video, so thank you, now
subscribe to the white channel, let's start,
you have to go to your
email, select your Rishi Laddu from above,
select the rise of God in Kaliyuga, you have to click on campus
and write an email, we have fun for the
customer, so what do you have to write in the subject,
click on campus, here to
make a lot, I will tell you everything, so you have to
look at it carefully, when you have to
write, first I will show you by writing
in the subject, please cancel, take this much,
please cancel,
see if it is
ICICI Prudential,
I will write any of your policies here,
you have to write the same in the initial, so here life is your
health or any work done, at least you have to take,
I will write your life, whatever
my ah, ah, yes, in this
you have to write in the subject,
write in campus  By taking Impossible, you have to
write the report here, what is the
full name of the person, surname along with
last name, a
topper, whatever is in the PAN card,
write it completely in the
PAN card, I will take you the PAN card, Aadhar
card, whatever is your name in it,
click on Net Insurance, in the receipt you
got, I have put the number and name in it also,
you can see that below, I will tell you what you have to write,
let's see, that is why
now you have to take out your policy number,
you will get the policy number in the receipt,
or
you have to enter the policy number properly,
today we will give you the policy
number to request, so below you will have to
request the money, so first
you take the mobile number, you
can message us from the mobile number there, a confirmation email will come
and if anything comes to you, you can also
tell us by messaging here what you have or
not, believe me, the
message will also come to the user can stop the mobile number, you
enter your mobile number, so
I cannot see, for this you will
enter it in the bar, I will reduce it
You can change your mobile
number by paying Rs. 1000 and below this
I am going to tell you what to write
in the request, I am going to tell you that in the request,
please cancel, I will
first write ICICI Prudential and show it to you, so let's
please cancel,
see this ICICI, you have ICICI Prudential
Life Insurance Policy,
you can also write the same, by doing this you will have to
send it here, I will tell you, I will give you the email
ID, don't worry, now
take it here, now I will definitely present you the mail,
see lifelines.co.uk,
this is the mail for testing, I will
take you to the description below, you can go
there and see in the description,
you can copy it from there, you can send it on this, from
there you will get it from the customer side
and you request the ticket number, track number, that will keep getting
processed, so with this
you will know what happened to you, what did
not happen, it reached here, but you will get to
know when you will get the return, let me
send it back, by doing this I will tell you here  It
takes some time to get Malaika,
you will get it in 2 hours, so
how did you like the video, subscribe if it does
not go white.